Let's select this heading right here out of the DOM.
لنحدد هذا العنوان من DOM هنا.
Now this gray color is pretty on brand,
هذا اللون الرمادي مناسب إلى حد ما،
but let's make it something exciting like orange.
لكن لنختار لونًا حيويًا مثل اللون البرتقالي.
We can see that running this command has changed our text to Orange,
يمكننا أن نرى أن تشغيل هذا الأمر قد غيّر النص إلى اللون البرتقالي،
and now it has a style property right here.
وأصبح له الآن خاصية نمطية هنا.
And if we open up this,
وفي حالة فتح ذلك،
we can see that it has a style right here.
يمكننا أن نرى أنه يحتوي على نمط هنا.
Now let's give ourselves a bit more room here.
لنعط أنفسنا مساحة أكبر قليلًا هنا.
Our heading looks pretty good right now but it is quite tiny.
يبدو عنواننا جيدًا الآن ولكنه صغيرًا للغاية.
So let's bump up the font size,
حسنًا لنكبِّر حجم الخط،
much better and we can see the font size right here and right here.
أصبح الأمر أفضل الآن، يمكننا رؤية حجم الخط هنا وهنا.
Let's check out heading dot style to see what it shows us.
لنتحقق من العنوان نقطة النمط لمعرفة ما يظهر لنا.
We can see that this property returns a CSS style declaration.
يمكننا معرفة أن هذه الخاصية ترجع إعلان أنماط CSS.
And let's open that up,
دعونا نفتح ذلك،
scrolling through this we see that most of these things are empty.
بالتمرير خلال ذلك، سنرى أن معظم هذه الأشياء فارغة.
There's our color that we added.
يوجد اللون الذي أضفناه.
And somewhere down here is going to be the font size there it is.
وفي مكان ما هنا سيوجد حجم الخط، ها هو.
If we scroll back up a bit there should be a section.
وإذا مررنا للأعلى قليلًا مرة أخرى، يجب أن يكون هناك جزءًا.
This CSS text will actually look at that in just a few minutes.
سيطلع نص CSS هذا على ذلك بالفعل في بضع دقائق.